<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on </title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Install Hugo in Windows</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/content/post/2020/install-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/content/post/2020/install-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Hugo comes in three versions: Standard, Extended, and Extended/Deploy. The Standard edition covers core functionalities, while Extended adds advanced options, with Extended/Deploy** offering further deployment features.&#xA;Setting Up Your Directories Open File Explorer and create a folder, e.g., C:\Hugo, and inside it, a bin folder. Installing Hugo Download the latest Hugo executable from Hugo releases.&#xA;Extract the contents into ..\Hugo\bin.&#xA;Open Command Prompt as Administrator and add Hugo to the PATH:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to use Lightbi theme ?</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/content/post/2020/use-this-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/content/post/2020/use-this-theme/</guid>
      <description>In this post, we&amp;rsquo;ll cover how to install Hugo and set up your first website with the Lightbi theme. For detailed steps, refer to Hugo’s quick-start guide.&#xA;Create a New Hugo Site hugo new site &amp;lt;name of site&amp;gt; cd &amp;lt;name of site&amp;gt; git init git submodule add https://github.com/binokochumolvarghese/lightbi-hugo themes/lightbi-hugo echo &amp;#34;theme = &amp;#39;lightbi-hugo&amp;#39;&amp;#34; &amp;gt;&amp;gt; config.toml hugo server After the above copy the contents of exampleSite to the content folder in your website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Features of Lightbi</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/content/post/2020/features-of-lightbi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/content/post/2020/features-of-lightbi/</guid>
      <description>General Three Main Content Sections:&#xA;Blog Notes Collections (Newsletter) Responsive Design:&#xA;Built with a mobile-first approach for seamless viewing on any device. Card-Based Theme:&#xA;Flexible image placement options: Image at the top of the card Image in the middle of the card Image at the bottom of the card No image option Menu Location Indicator:&#xA;Clear visual cues for active menu items. Multilingual Support:&#xA;Includes a language selector for easy switching between languages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>More about Lightbi</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/content/post/2020/more-about-lightbi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/content/post/2020/more-about-lightbi/</guid>
      <description>Wiki Checkout the wiki page for detailed documentation of the theme features.&#xA;Support &amp;amp; Contribution Star 🌟 this repository to show your support! Help spread the word about Hugo Lightbi by sharing it on social media and recommending it to your friends and colleagues. Found a bug? Report it via GitHub Issues to help us improve. Have feature ideas? Start a conversation in GitHub Discussions. Got questions? Ask away in our GitHub Discussions community.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parameters in Lightbi</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/content/post/2020/parameters/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/content/post/2020/parameters/</guid>
      <description>Below is a list of configurable parameters in the Lightbi theme, along with descriptions to help you customize your site effectively. You can be adjust the below parameters in your hugo.toml file.&#xA;Theme Parameters readingTime&#xA;Type: Boolean (true or false) Description: When set to true, displays an estimated reading time for each post. This helps readers gauge how long it will take to read the content. wordCount&#xA;Type: Boolean Description: Enables or disables the word count display for each post.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
